<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Home &amp; Blog</title>
    <link>http://www.nicolabernardelli.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Home &amp; Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2015 18:17:50 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://www.nicolabernardelli.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Stainless steel</title>
      <link>http://www.nicolabernardelli.com/blog/2015/08/18/stainless-steel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2015 18:17:50 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.nicolabernardelli.com/blog/2015/08/18/stainless-steel/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:)&lt;/strong&gt; Nestor&amp;rsquo;s is fine, the surgery was a success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Carola tells us that he entered the operating room as &lt;em&gt;up&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;arriba&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; as he was when I saw him last Sunday&amp;hellip; &lt;strong&gt;stainless steel character indeed!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(How comes he was nervous before certain concerts, then, I can &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; understand.)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cajón unplugged</title>
      <link>http://www.nicolabernardelli.com/blog/2015/08/16/caj%C3%B3n-unplugged/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2015 16:13:18 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.nicolabernardelli.com/blog/2015/08/16/caj%C3%B3n-unplugged/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have just arrived from the hospital and I can confirm that Nestor&amp;rsquo;s mood is &lt;em&gt;quite fine&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He &lt;strong&gt;unplugged&lt;/strong&gt; himself from the monitoring system, he grabbed a wood box very similar to a &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;cajón&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Caj%C3%B3n&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Wikipedia article&lt;/a&gt;) and started playing sitting on it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The nurse, who had been focusing on another patient, soon realized and came to stop the show. Alas, I can &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; publish any pictures, she told us that it is forbidden to shoot any in there, and I don&amp;rsquo;t want to risk causing her any trouble. According to her, Nestor&amp;rsquo;s very positive mood will be of great help. The intervention is confirmed for Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I forgot to ask what the wood box was for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Admittedly I should publish these articles in Spanish, as a priority (or Castellano to be more precise), although we &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; have friends abroad (mostly people who kept in touch after travelling to Buenos Aires and picking up our show in the list of acts&amp;hellip; from Brasil, South Africa, Denmark, the USA&amp;hellip;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My previous website was multilingual and I plan to do the same on this one, at least for the most &amp;ldquo;static&amp;rdquo; content&amp;hellip; As for the blog&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;ll figure out&amp;hellip; separate pages separate comments, or translated content sharing the same comments&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many high traffic websites receive comments in any languages on the same page, they do not separate by language&amp;hellip; and as I&amp;rsquo;m constantly very busy I don&amp;rsquo;t plan to make of this website a high traffic forum, although giving the chance to leave comments seems a &lt;em&gt;very&lt;/em&gt; nice feature to me. Honestly, I&amp;rsquo;m very tempted to leave the blog section &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; multilingual. Suggestions are welcome at this stage anyway.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heart attack</title>
      <link>http://www.nicolabernardelli.com/blog/2015/08/13/heart-attack/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2015 13:58:23 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.nicolabernardelli.com/blog/2015/08/13/heart-attack/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This &lt;em&gt;Blog&lt;/em&gt; starts with a heart attack. &lt;strong&gt;Nestor Astarita&lt;/strong&gt;, drummer and leader of the &lt;strong&gt;Tribute to Miles Davis and Astor Piazzolla&lt;/strong&gt; project, has just suffered one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why not &amp;ldquo;sadly&amp;rdquo;? Because, even under this circumstance, «He&amp;rsquo;s as &lt;em&gt;up&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;arriba&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;, as he always is». Carola Faverio, his life mate, transmits news to us, we are not allowed to visit him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He&amp;rsquo;s facing an urgent intervention today or tomorrow, which of course implies serious risks. &lt;strong&gt;Best luck Nestor!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nestor&amp;rsquo;s manager of choice wants us to comply with our engagement with the club anyway, and not cancel on such short notice, but the possible replacement drummer he was thinking of was not available. So he asked me, and I proposed &lt;strong&gt;Quintino Cinalli&lt;/strong&gt;, who is also a hell of a drummer. I&amp;rsquo;ll be in the club a bit earlier tonight to check with him the list of themes and the arrangements we have in some points (many themes widely change on the fly from one concert to another, anyway).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EDIT, good news:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last message from Carola (14h54 local time Buenos Aires UTC-3):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hi! Medical report: he&amp;rsquo;s very fine, already stable, so they are planning the intervention for next Tuesday. He will stay in CCU as a safety measure. Thanks for sharing the blood donors&amp;rsquo; call. Today he can already wear a pijama, so I might send you a picture, but only if he looks pretty, you know he&amp;rsquo;s always taking care of style LOL. Thanks for your love and support, a huge hug!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Original text in &lt;em&gt;Castellano&lt;/em&gt; from Carola:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Holaa! parte medico: esta m bien, ya estabilizado, entonces programan operación para el martes. Seguirá en unidad coronaria por prevención. Gracias por publicar el pedido de dadores de sangre.  Hoy ya puede usar pijama así que a lo mejor, si esta bonito les comparto una foto, saben q es recoqueto, jaja. Gracias por el cariño y el apoyo, un enorme abrazo!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>