<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Home &amp; Blog</title>
    <link>http://www.nicolabernardelli.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Home &amp; Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2015 16:13:18 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://www.nicolabernardelli.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Cajón unplugged</title>
      <link>http://www.nicolabernardelli.com/blog/2015/08/16/caj%C3%B3n-unplugged/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2015 16:13:18 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.nicolabernardelli.com/blog/2015/08/16/caj%C3%B3n-unplugged/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have just arrived from the hospital and I can confirm that Nestor mood is just &lt;em&gt;fine&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He &lt;strong&gt;unplugged&lt;/strong&gt; himself from the monitoring system, grabbed a wood box very similar to a &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Caj%C3%B3n&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;cajón&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and started playing on it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The nurse, who had been focusing on another patient, soon realized and came to stop the show and&amp;hellip; alas I can &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; publish any pictures, it&amp;rsquo;s just forbidden to take any in there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, according to the nurse Nestor&amp;rsquo;s very positive mood might be of great help. The intervention is confirmed for Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I forgot to ask what was that wood box for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Admittedly I should publish these articles in Spanish as a priority&amp;hellip; although we &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; have friends abroad (mostly people who kept in touch after travelling in Buenos Aires and seeing our show&amp;hellip; from Brasil, South Africa, Denmark, the USA&amp;hellip;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My previous website was multilingual and I plan to do the same on this one, at least for the most &amp;ldquo;static&amp;rdquo; content&amp;hellip; As for the blog&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;ll figure out&amp;hellip; separate pages separate comments, or translated content sharing the same comments&amp;hellip; many high traffic websites receive comments in any language anyway, they do not separate by language&amp;hellip; and admittedly I&amp;rsquo;m constantly short of time and I don&amp;rsquo;t plan to make of this website a high traffic forum, although giving the chance to leave comments seems a nice feature to me. Honestly, I&amp;rsquo;m very tempt to leave the blog section &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; multilingual.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heart attack</title>
      <link>http://www.nicolabernardelli.com/blog/2015/08/13/heart-attack/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2015 13:58:23 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.nicolabernardelli.com/blog/2015/08/13/heart-attack/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This &lt;em&gt;Blog&lt;/em&gt; starts with a heart attack. &lt;strong&gt;Nestor Astarita&lt;/strong&gt;, drummer and leader of the &lt;strong&gt;Tribute to Miles Davis and Astor Piazzolla&lt;/strong&gt; project, has just suffered one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why not &amp;ldquo;sadly&amp;rdquo;? Because, even under this circumstance, &amp;ldquo;he&amp;rsquo;s as &lt;em&gt;up&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;arriba&lt;/em&gt;, as he always is&amp;rdquo;. Carola Faverio, his life mate, transmits news to us, we are not allowed to visit him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He&amp;rsquo;s facing an urgent intervention today or tomorrow, which of course implies serious risks. &lt;strong&gt;Best luck Nestor!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nestor&amp;rsquo;s manager of choice wants us to comply with our engagement with the club anyway, and not cancel on such short notice, but the possible replacement drummer he was thinking of was not available. So he asked me, and I proposed &lt;strong&gt;Quintino Cinalli&lt;/strong&gt;, who is also a hell of a drummer. I&amp;rsquo;ll be in the club a bit earlier tonight to check with him the list of themes and the arrangements we have in some points (many themes widely change on the fly from one concert to another, anyway).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EDIT, good news:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last message from Carola (14h54 local time Buenos Aires UTC-3):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hi! Medical report: he&amp;rsquo;s very fine, already stable, so they are planning the intervention for next Tuesday. He will stay in CCU as a safety measure. Thanks for sharing the blood donors&amp;rsquo; call. Today he can already wear a pijama, so I might send you a picture, but only if he looks pretty, you know he&amp;rsquo;s always taking care of style LOL. Thanks for your love and support, a huge hug!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Original text in &lt;em&gt;Castellano&lt;/em&gt; from Carola:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Holaa! parte medico: esta m bien, ya estabilizado, entonces programan operación para el martes. Seguirá en unidad coronaria por prevención. Gracias por publicar el pedido de dadores de sangre.  Hoy ya puede usar pijama así que a lo mejor, si esta bonito les comparto una foto, saben q es recoqueto, jaja. Gracias por el cariño y el apoyo, un enorme abrazo!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>